We are nearing the end of the 6th National Youth Football Tournament.
After 40 minutes, neither team could become champion.
The fierce match continued with the first and second extra time periods.
And now we have entered the final 5 minutes!
The 11 players of Nankatsu and Meiwa are giving it their all...
...but the score is 2-2!
Will there be a side that seizes victory?
Or will both teams become champions?
The final kick-off of the tournament will take place with the referee's whistle.
As we promised, we didn't concede a goal in the first half.
The rest is up to you, Tsubasa and Misaki.
Tsubasa! Misaki!
In the second half, we're entrusting it to the golden duo!
Even if my leg breaks, I'll play until the very last moment!
I will definitely score.
Otherwise, I will have wasted everyone's efforts in the first half!
Bring it on!
I'd rather die than concede a goal.
We won't lose.
No matter what kind of plan you've made!
We'll just attack!
Let's go, Misaki-kun!
Okay!
The scent of the grass when I stumbled
The endless blue sky stretched out above me
This winding and random road
Is a map for our endless dreams
Even if hope misses its target
As long as I get back up, my dreams will never end
Number one! Get out in front, ahead of everyone
Start running, with your tricky play, towards the world stage! Start! Dash!
Run & Run!
Only our aspirations are the signals that move us, bit by bit
Blaze, blaze, blaze and launch the kick
Jump out onto the huge TV screen
Episode 27:
Time for Victory
Translation: ARE-YOU-SURE
AreyousureSubs Presents
The last 5 minutes!
Push, Nankatsu!
Don't you lose, Meiwa!
You are definitely the champions!
Come on! We'll attack until the very last moment!
We'll steal the ball and go on the attack!
We'll show Meiwa's football until the end!
Yes!
Tsubasa-kun dribbles past.
Wonderful moves showing that he rested in the first half!
I will definitely score!
Misaki-kun!
Now he also tricks his opponents and makes a great pass!
I won't allow it!
He dodges! Misaki-kun's movements are excellent too!
Nankatsu's golden duo is revived!
Alright, we can do this!
He lost his balance!
The injury on his leg seems serious.
Misaki-kun!
Hyuga-kun steps forward and gets the ball.
Alright, we'll score the goal!
Yes!
While Hyuga-kun advances quickly through the middle, Meiwa launches a fast attack!
Will Misaki really not be able to handle it?
Taro...
Everyone! Stay calm!
Believe in Misaki!
He will definitely pull it off!
We'll stop this attack!
Yes.
I won't allow it!
Do your best, kids!
My leg has reached its limit too.
But I have to stop this Meiwa attack right here.
I beg you. Hold on just a little longer, my leg.
Everyone is doing this for me...
Damn it!
Was this going to be the end of Misaki Taro?
Give me one last strength.
Dad!
Mom!
Hyuga-san!
Oh no!
The unmarked Hyuga-kun receives the pass!
Hyuga-kun shoots!
Will it be a goal?!
No, he blocks it!
Tsubasa-kun stops Hyuga-kun's shot!
What?!
Tsubasa!
Misaki-kun, counter-attack!
To Misaki-kun, who couldn't fully commit to the game because of his leg injury...
...Tsubasa-kun still sends the pass.
My one and only partner is Misaki-kun.
You can do it, Misaki-kun!
Let's show our final golden duo play!
Tsubasa-kun.
Dad!
Mom!
This is my final play!
Misaki-kun moves forward, enduring the pain in his leg!
What?!
Misaki!
Misaki-kun!
Tsubasa-kun is right behind him!
There it is, finally!
This is the play of Nankatsu's golden duo!
A wonderful passing synchronization that will confound the defense!
Misaki-kun, keep it up!
Take this, Wakashimazu!
However, it's not a goal!
You're the man, Wakashimazu!
I'll take it.
Ishizaki-kun saves the ball.
Ishizaki-kun!
Tsubasa! Misaki!
Count me in too!
Take it!
Ishizaki-kun sends a cross.
However, Hyuga-kun is there to stop it.
I'm coming!
This is Misaki-kun's overhead kick!
Misaki!
But their timing is completely off!
What?!
Tsubasa-kun!
While Misaki-kun did it to set a trap, Tsubasa-kun goes for the overhead kick!
The late-arriving overhead kick of Nankatsu's golden duo!
Go!
I-It's in! Goal!
- You did it!
- Amazing, Tsubasa!
Wonderful goal!
- That's it!
- We did it!
Nankatsu's golden duo displays wonderful teamwork.
A minute and a half of the final extra time has passed...
...and Nankatsu finally takes the lead!
Tsubasa! Misaki!
Wakabayashi-san's plan worked.
- Tsubasa!
- Tsubasa...
Hyuga-kun was tricked by Misaki-kun's jump.
He couldn't stop Tsubasa-kun's overhead kick.
Even Wakashimazu-kun was unable to react to this shot.
Damn it!
The teamwork of Nankatsu's golden duo is perfect!
Misaki-kun...
Tsubasa-kun!
Well done, Taro.
Taro...
But there are still 3 minutes left.
No one expects the merciless tiger, Hyuga-kun, to give up.
Don't lose, Kojiro.
Don't lose hope!
Big brother...
Kojiro...
That's to be expected from Tsubasa and Misaki.
You display teamwork as if you're communicating mentally.
But I haven't lost yet!
Meiwa FC immediately goes on the attack with the kick-off!
They have the determination to equalize!
Everyone! Don't lower your guard just because we're ahead!
Stay focused!
Okay!
Just hold on a little longer. I beg you.
Grit your teeth, Misaki-kun.
Just a little more.
Yes.
Tsubasa... Misaki...
You taught me that I can't play football alone.
Hyuga-san!
And also that football isn't just about power.
But most importantly, what I felt while fighting against you...
...was the true joy of football!
Football is truly very enjoyable.
Hyuga-kun advances quickly towards the Nankatsu goal.
Meiwa's attack is very balanced.
Stop them!
Don't let him get close!
Until now, I fought only for my family or to win.
But while you were my opponents, I tasted the true joy of playing football.
This time Hyuga-kun breaks through with his power!
Even so...
...I can't give up on winning!
My football aims for victory.
It's an undefeated football!
A tackle from Ishizaki-kun!
But Hyuga-kun jumps and dodges it with wonderful timing!
Even if it's fun, it's meaningless if you lose!
Hyuga-kun immediately gets into shooting position!
In this situation, I can't let you score!
Tsubasa!
Tsubasa-kun jumps to block it!
Take it, Takeshi!
Hyuga-kun makes a quick decision and passes instead of shooting!
The unmarked Sawada-kun runs.
A goal chance for Meiwa!
Sawada-kun shoots!
Wakabayashi-kun saves it once again!
You did it!
Nice catch, Wakabayashi-san!
Despite it being a huge chance for Meiwa, with goalkeeper Wakabayashi-kun's good play...
...they still couldn't find the goal!
I'm sorry, Hyuga-san.
Don't worry about it, Takeshi.
We still have 2 minutes.
If I shoot every minute, we can win.
Just like Tsubasa and Misaki, Wakabayashi's leg is also injured.
It was clear from the last save that his injury was serious.
If I can shoot comfortably, I can break through the wall Wakabayashi has built.
We can win this match!
Translation: ARE-YOU-SURE
AreyousureSubs Presents
Nankatsu still leads 3-2.
Only 2 minutes left.
The final match is about to be decided!
That goal was my fault.
I'll make up for it by doing karate!
Nankatsu will win if they hold onto the ball for the remaining time. What will happen?!
Let's go, Wakabayashi-kun!
I'll keep attacking!
Alright, take it!
Wakabayashi-kun collapses on the ground as he tries to throw the ball!
Wakabayashi-san!
It was clear there was pain in his left leg, but Wakabayashi-kun had never seemed to be in this much pain!
Now!
Taking advantage of this opportunity, Meiwa's Sawada-kun runs towards the goal!
I won't allow it!
Takasugi-kun clears it.
Nankatsu averted a huge danger.
But Wakabayashi-kun still hasn't been able to get up.
Damn it! Is this as far as it goes?
Genzo!
Morisaki, start warming up.
Okay!
Alright, that's it!
Wakabayashi is gone now.
As long as I shoot, it will be a goal.
Meiwa gets the cleared ball.
Let's go! Here's the chance!
Meiwa FC advances quickly towards the goal with a fast attack!
Everyone, we have to prevent them from shooting no matter what!
We'll get the ball back!
Yes!
Nankatsu captain Tsubasa-kun directs the defense and tightens it!
While it's impossible for Wakabayashi-kun to continue playing...
...Nankatsu brings on substitute goalkeeper Morisaki.
But a substitution can only be made when the ball is out of play or...
...when the game is stopped due to a foul.
As I thought, Nankatsu will take Wakabayashi off.
I have to score before that happens!
Hyuga-kun runs towards the goal!
But Misaki-kun is right behind him!
I may not be able to continue playing duo play with Tsubasa-kun.
But I'll still defend!
I'll play for Nankatsu until the last drop of my strength!
I'll mark Kojiro!
Star player Hyuga-kun is tightly marked by Misaki-kun!
Meiwa can't pass!
Here!
Let's steal the ball!
Damn it! Nankatsu is as stubborn as ever!
At this rate, it's over for us! We have to do something!
Less than a minute left.
Stop them!
Will Nankatsu continue to prevent Meiwa from shooting?
Damn it!
What is Meiwa doing?!
Goalkeeper Wakashimazu-kun is coming!
I'll score the equalizing goal!
Meiwa pushes forward for one final attack with the whole team!
Wakashimazu!
Takeshi!
Taking advantage of Misaki-kun's momentary lapse of attention, Hyuga-kun gets free!
Hyuga-san!
Hyuga-kun receives the ball!
Alright, got it!
What?!
I won't allow it!
Tsubasa-kun fights for the ball with his last remaining strength!
Will Tsubasa-kun's sliding tackle come early...
...or Hyuga-kun's shot?!
The final struggle!
His shot was faster!
A jumping volley from Hyuga-kun!
Is it going in or not?!
Damn it...
I'm not going to give up.
Only my left leg hurts.
I still have one good leg!
He jumps using his right foot!
What?!
But he can't reach it!
He saved it!
Wakabayashi-san!
After jumping with his right foot, using his hand...
...he extended his reach and cleared the ball!
Meiwa can't equalize!
Alright, I'll clear it!
I won't allow it!
This is the karate move called the flying kick!
At this rate, they'll equalize!
That's it!
N-No way...
I can't let it go in.
I can't let this shot go in.
I have to stop it no matter what!
We will win!
He stopped it!
He stopped it right on the goal line!
What?!
A perfect play from Misaki-kun!
Meiwa can't score again!
But Misaki-kun hits his head on the goal post because of his speed!
Misaki!
If he hadn't run, he wouldn't have been able to stop the ball.
He took on this task fully aware that this would happen.
Misaki-kun displays a wonderful play, sacrificing himself!
Misaki-kun...
Tsubasa-kun...
Tsubasa.
Tsubasa...
TSUBASA!
The ball is still in play!
There are 30 seconds left in the match!
Meiwa runs towards the ball for one final chance!
Tsubasa!
Tsubasa-kun is still on the attack!
He dribbles the ball towards the Meiwa goal all by himself!
Tsubasa!
Fall back!
Meiwa can't get the ball!
How much energy does this small body have?!
Besides, wasn't Tsubasa-kun's left leg injured?!
Blessed with football talent, Ozora Tsubasa-kun is putting on a one-man fight right now!
Tsubasa! Tsubasa! Tsubasa! Tsubasa!
We lost the first match against Meiwa 7-6.
And now in the final, we're leading 3-2.
So our battle is tied!
We need one more goal to truly become champions.
We'll score one more goal and become the true champions!
Then I...
Then I'll go to Brazil!
Stop him, Takeshi!
Okay!
I won't lose the ball to anyone!
I won't stop until I score!
What happened, Sawada-kun?!
He's backing away without even reacting.
What fiery eyes...
Only a few seconds left.
Tsubasa, this is our final battle!
I'll steal the ball from you and put everything I have into a long shot from here.
Bring it on, Hyuga Kojiro!
I won't lose!
A huge collision occurs!
This is their final confrontation!
He got past!
In the final confrontation, Tsubasa-kun crushes him not with technique, but with strength!
I lost...
Now it's only up to Wakashimazu-kun.
One more goal...
Damn it!
Tsubasa-kun quickly prepares to shoot!
Wakashimazu-kun leaps towards the ball!
Instead of shooting, Tsubasa-kun jumps and dodges him!
What?!
He passed!
In front of Tsubasa-kun, there is only the Meiwa goal!
Thus, Nankatsu will seize victory!
The ball tears through the net and rises into the sky!
And the whistle blows to end the match!
We did it, Tsubasa!
We won! We won!
We are the champions!
You did it!
Tsubasa-kun!
After 7 days of struggle, Nankatsu SC emerges victorious.
Tsubasa, congratulations.
You finally did it, didn't you?
Misaki, it's over.
We did it.
We won.
Yes.
Wakabayashi-san!
Misaki, we won!
Wakabayashi-san, we did it!
Nankatsu SC truly gave it their all.
Their faces are shining after victory!
Even though they lost, Meiwa FC also put up a really good fight.
We lost...
Though they couldn't become champions, they came in second.
Meiwa FC truly gave it their all.
You did a great job, Meiwa!
Second place is also good!
Well done, Kojiro.
Big brother...
So Nankatsu won.
I guess we'll be requesting Tsubasa-kun.
Yes.
Hyuga-san...
Tsubasa.
This was to be expected.
I lost, Tsubasa.
What?
Hyuga-kun...
I didn't expect you to get past me using your strength at the very last moment.
You completely scattered me.
You deserved to win this match.
Hyuga-kun...
Hyuga-san!
Misaki, even I couldn't have formed as good a duo with Tsubasa as you did.
Kojiro...
Get that leg healed right away.
Wakabayashi, in the end I couldn't score against you from outside the penalty area.
But in our next encounter, I will definitely score against you. Remember that.
Okay. I'll be looking forward to it.
You defeated me terribly.
For the first time, I conceded 4 goals in a match.
Led by Hyuga-kun and Tsubasa-kun, right now...
...the Nankatsu and Meiwa players are shaking hands and congratulating each other.
The two teams that fought for over 60 minutes...
...are freely expressing their emotions.
The Youth Football Tournament ends with Nankatsu's victory.
However, above all else, we hope that every team...
...has built bonds of friendship that will last from now on.
You did it, Tsubasa.
Congratulations, Misaki.
Congratulations, Tsubasa-kun.
Tsubasa, I congratulate you.
Right now, there is simply nothing I can say.
You have matured greatly in this tournament.
You faced a wide variety of opponents, learned a lot from them, and...
...you were able to advance all the way to the end.
And as you promised, you became the champion of the National Tournament.
But Tsubasa, I can't keep the promise I made to you.
If I win, we'll go to Brazil, Roberto!
This is a farewell, Tsubasa.
A star passes by with a stern look
The whole town is buzzing that he's a remarkable person
Butterfly samba, zigzag samba
The rumors about him even make the samba run
And as for us, what are we doing here?
Going crazy over just one ball
Dash, dash, dash
Kick and dash
Someday we'll nail it, a lightning shot
At that moment, I'll be a super hero
Dash, dash, dash
Kick and dash
Blaze with youth and run through
Next Episode 28:
Time to Say Goodbye to Everyone